i know i don't want to
be the one that you run to
when you got nowhere else to go
when you need some love
i know i'm the last one
you try to call
but i always give in
to give you it all
i can't be your midnight love
when your silver is my gold
in this light
i swear i'm blind
i swear you're mine
i hope that the right time
one day arrives
so i'll be willing
to let this die
able to look you
right in the eyes
and say i'm not
your consolation prize
i can't be your midnight love
when your silver is my gold
in this light
i swear i'm blind
i swear you're mine
i can't be your second best
close but not your favorite
i keep going back for more
where there's nothing from before